要记住
Remember…
我爱你
I love you.
我爱你 托马斯
I love you, Thomas.
妈妈
Mom!
托马斯
Thomas…
没事的
it's okay.
不 不要
No, no, no!
托马斯
Thomas!
快醒醒 我们得马上走 快
Wake up! We gotta go! Come on!
我们走 我们要走了 快
Let's go! Let's go! We gotta go!
你还好吗 没事吧
You all right? You all right?
等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait!
你去哪里
Where are you going?
我们没时间了
We don't have time!
来吧
Come on!
离开这里
Get out of here!
毒虫 有毒虫
Cranks! We got Cranks!
马上转移 这里不安全 孩子
Gotta move! Not safe out here, kid!
这里有一大群
Got a swarm to the flank!
走 孩子们 快走
Go, kid! Go, go!
设置一条警戒线 让他们退到右边
Set a perimeter! Hold them back on the right side!
好了孩子们 我们走吧 快走
Come on, kids, let's go! Let's go! Move it! Come on!
一直走 不要停
Keep moving! Keep moving!
带他们离开 这里安全了
Tell him to take off! We're clear!
《移动迷宫2：焦土试炼》
你们没事吧
You kids doing all right?
我对所有的事情很抱歉 我们要对付那群东西
Sorry about all the fuss. We had ourselves a bit of a swarm.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是你们还活着的原因
I'm the reason you're all still alive.
让你们活着也是我的目的
It's my intention to keep you that way.
现在跟我来吧 我们会带你们去走走
Now, come with me. We'll get you kids squared away.
你们可以叫我詹森先生 这地方是由我来负责的
You can call me Mr. Janson. I run this place.
对我们来说这是个避难所 不受外面恐怖的世界侵害
For us it is a sanctuary, safe from the horrors of the outside world.
你们都应该把这当作是一个中转站
You all should think of it as a way station.
两个家之间的另一个家 看着点
Kind of a home between homes. Watch yourselves.
而你是带我们回家的
That mean you're taking us home?
各种各样的家
A home of sorts.
不幸的是 无论你来自哪里都没多少人生存了
Sadly, there wouldn't be much left of wherever you came from.
但我们有一个适合你们的地方
But we do have a place for you.
在外面焦土区的一个避难所
A refuge, outside the Scorch,
一个实验部永远也不会找到你们的地方
where WICKED will never find you again.
这听起来怎么样
How does that sound?
为什么你要帮我们
Why are you helping us?
我们就说这世界在一个相当危险的形势吧
Let's just say the world out there is in a rather precarious situation.
我们都命悬一线
We're all hanging on by a very thin thread.
事实上你们可以从闪焰病毒幸存下来
The fact that you kids can survive the Flare virus…
就是成为人类继续生存的最好希望
makes you the best chance of humanity's continued survival.
不幸的是 这同时也让你们成为目标
Unfortunately, it also makes you a target,
毫无疑问你们现在已经注意到了
as no doubt by now you've noticed.
越过这门就是你们新生活的开始
Beyond this door lies the beginning of your new lives.
第一件事
First things first…
就让我们先解决体味的问题
let's do something about that smell.
哦 天啊
Oh, man!
感觉真好
Feels great!
费平 感觉怎么样
Frypan, how you feel over there?
等等 这是什么
Wait, what is that?
一点餐前开胃菜 钙 叶酸 维生素A到Z
Just a little cocktail. Calcium, folate, vitamins A through Z.
几乎都是你在外面一直缺少的营养
Pretty much everything you've been deprived of out there.
尽量放松
Try to relax.
你确定你取够血了吗
Sure you got enough there?
晚上好 克劳福德医生
Evening, Dr. Crawford.
晚上好 新来的人适应的怎么样
Good evening. How are the new arrivals holding up?
目前来说还不错
So far, so good.
好吧
All right.
你一定是特丽莎了
And you must be Teresa.
托马斯
Thomas?
什么事
Yeah?
请跟我来
Come with me, please.
托马斯
Thomas,
很感谢你来见我
thank you for seeing me.
很抱歉麻烦到你…
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
我只是希望我们 可以远离他们就我们两人谈谈
I was just hoping we might get a moment to chat in private, away from the others.
那么…
Well…
我不会用你太多时间
I won't take up too much of your time.
其实我只有一个问题
I really only have one question.
你还记得实验部些什么
What do you remember about WICKED?
你没有惹上麻烦
You're not in trouble.
我只是在谈谈 只是想搞清楚
We're just having a conversation. I'm just trying to understand.
搞清楚什么
Understand what?
你是站在哪一边的
Whose side are you on?
我记得我以前是给实验部工作的
I remember I used to work for WICKED.
我记得他们送我进迷宫
I remember that they sent me into the maze.
我记得 我看着我的朋友在我面前死
I remember watching my friends die in front of me.
我是他们那边的
I'm on their side.
有意思
Interesting.
你说你曾经为实验部工作 但他们送你进迷宫
You say you worked for WICKED, but they sent you into the maze.
为什么他们会这么做
Why would they do something like that?
我不知道 也许你应该在杀他们之前问他们
I don't know. Maybe you should've asked them before you killed them all.
我会谨记这一点
I'll be sure to keep that in mind.
享受你在这里休息吧
Enjoy the rest of your stay.
就这样
That's it?
对 你已经说了所有我需要知道的了
Yeah, you've told me everything I need to know.
你和你的朋友都被没问题 可以加入到其他人
You and your friends have all been cleared to join the others.
很快你们会去到更好的地方
Soon you'll all be moving on to greener pastures.
等等
Wait.
其他人
Others?
嘿 托马斯
Hey, Thomas!
嘿 米诺怎么回事
Hey, Minho, what's going on?
迷宫不止一个 来吧
We weren't the only maze. Come on.
有一声巨大的爆炸 而这些人不知从哪里冒出来的
And there was this big, loud explosion, and these guys came out of nowhere.
他们在那开始开枪扫射
Started shooting up the place.
非常激烈
It was intense.
他们把我们带出迷宫 然后带我们来这里
They pulled us out of the maze and brought us here.
那其他人呢
What about the rest?
其他留在迷宫里的人 他们怎么样了
The other people left behind in the maze, what happened to them?
我不知道
I don't know.
我猜实验部还留着他们
I guess WICKED still has them.
- 你们在这多长时间了 - 没多久
- How long you guys been here? - Not long.
只有1或2天
Just a day or two.
在那里的那个孩子 他在这里最久
That kid over there has been here the longest.
几乎一个星期了
Almost a week.
他的迷宫就只有女孩子
His maze was nothing but girls.
真的吗
Really?
有些人就是运气好
Some guys have all the luck.
晚上好 先生们 女士们
Good evening, gentlemen. Ladies.
你们知道该怎么做 如果你听到你的名字
You all know how this works. If you hear your name called…
请有序的站起来 然后来我身后的同事这边…
please rise in an orderly fashion, join my colleagues behind me…
他们会护送你们去东侧
where they will escort you to the eastern wing.
你们的新生活即将开始
Your new lives are about to begin.
康纳
Connor.
伊夫林
Evelyn.
Ev!
贾斯廷
Jusfin.
彼得
Peter.
埃里森
Allison.
史昆纪
Squigee.
好了 安静下来
All right. Settle down.
富兰克林和阿比盖尔
Franklin. And Abigail.
现在 你们不要灰心 如果我可以带更多的人 我会的
Now, now, don't get discouraged. If I could take more, I would.
每天都有机会 会轮到你们的
There's always tomorrow. Your time will come.
继续吃饭吧
Go on, eat up.
他们要去哪里
Where are they going?
远离这里
Far from here.
这些混蛋真幸运
Lucky bastards.
类似农场的地方 一个安全的地方
Some kind of farm. A safe place.
他们一次只能带你们几个人去
They can only take in a couple of people at a time.
这到底怎么回事
What the hell?
嘿 特丽莎
Hey, Teresa?
特丽莎
Teresa!
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey…
他们要带她去哪里
Where are they taking her?
只是多做几个测试
They just have to run a few more tests.
别担心 他们很快就好了
Don't worry, they'll be done with her soon.
她还好吗
Is she okay?
她没事
She's fine.
我要上铺
I got top bunk.
太慢了
Too slow.
我可以习惯这个的
I could get used to this.
这不算差啊
Yeah. It's not bad.
你觉得这些人想从特丽莎身上得到什么
Hey, what do you think those guys want with Teresa?
我知道这女孩的一件事 就是她能照顾好自己的
Now, if there's one thing I know about that girl, she can take care of herself.
不用担心
Don't worry about it.
嘿
Hey.
下面
Down here.
天啊
Oh, my God.
快点 跟我来
Come on. Follow me.
什么啊
What?
快点 这边
Hurry, this way.
快点
Come on.
嘿 等一下 我们在干什么
Hey, wait a second. What the hell are we doing?
快点 我们要错过了
Come on, we're gonna miss it.
我到底在干什么
What the hell am I doing?
我们在这干什么
What are we doing?
过来这里
Come here.
看
Watch.
这到底是什么
What the hell was that?
他们每天晚上都带一个新的进来
They bring in new ones every night like clockwork.
那他们对他们做什么
You know what they do with them?
我不知道 这事我还没搞清楚
I don't know. This is as far as I've ever gotten.
那儿连排气管都没有
The vents don't even go into that section.
但自从他们进去后 他们就没再出来了
But once they go through that door, they don't come back out.
我想从来没有人可以离开这地方
I don't think anybody ever really leaves this place.
快点 我们要在有人发觉我们不见了之前回去
Come on. We've gotta go before somebody notices we're gone.
你为什么给我看这个
Why did you show me this?
因为也许其他人会听你的
Because maybe the others will listen to you.
这里有些怪异的事情 而我知道你也是这么认为的
There's something weird going on here. And I know you think so too.
嘿 等等
Hey, wait.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
阿里斯
Aris.
爱丽丝
Alice.
巴里
Barry.
沃尔特
Walt.
埃德加
Edgar.
萨曼莎
Samantha.
我想知道那门后是通往什么地方的
I wanna know what's through that door.
亚伦
Aaron.
不 我们已经讨论过这个了
Now, we've been over this.
你说他们被遮盖了 所以你不知道你看见的是什么
You said they were covered up, so you don't know what you saw.
- 丹尼斯 - 这可以是任何东西
- Dennis. - It could've been anything under there.
我知道我看见的是什么 他们是尸体
I know exactly what I saw. They were bodies.
莎莉
Sally.
阿里斯说他们每天晚上都带一批新的进去
Aris said they bring in a new batch every night.
他妈的阿里斯是谁啊
Who the hell is Aris?
亨利
Henry.
提姆
Tim.
好吧 我同意
Well, I'm sold.
还有最后一个但这不重要 大卫
And last but not least, David.
谢谢你们的配合 希望你今晚过的愉快
Thank you for your attention. Enjoy the rest of your evening.
好了 直到我们知道这是什么事之前 我们应该低调
Okay, until we know anything for certain, we should just keep our heads down…
尽量别引起任何注意 好吗
and try not to draw any attention to ourselves, all right?
他这是去干嘛
What is he doing?
我觉得他在引起注意
I think he's drawing attention to himself.
等一下 你没有被叫上
Hang on. You weren't called.
我知道 我就进去一下
I know, I'm just gonna be a second.
这是限制区域 孩子
This is a restricted area, kid.
我只是想去见我的朋友 你能让我过去吗
I just wanna see my friend. Can you let me through?
回到你的位子上
Get your ass back in that chair.
请记住 监视器会监视你们的一举一动 如果有谁违反规定
Just remember, you are always being monitored. Breaking the rules…
回去
Back off!
你怎么回事 到底怎么啦啊
What's your problem, man? What the hell, huh?
回去
Back off!
为什么你们不让人过去
Why won't you let me see her?
控制好你的朋友
Control your friend!
这里发生什么事
What's happening here?
托马斯
Thomas?
我认为我们可以互相信任
I thought we could trust each other.
你知道我们在这是一伙的
You know we're all on the same team here.
是吗
Are we?
带他们去他们的房
Get them to their bunks.
你们全部进去
Get your asses in there! All of you!
刚才那是怎么回事
What the hell was that about?
你不是真认为 他们会就这样让你过去吧
You didn't really think they were just gonna let you through?
不 当然不会
Nah, of course I didn't.
我要找出门的另一边是什么
I'm gonna find out what's on the other side of that door.
好吧
Right.
纽特 他们在隐藏了些东西 好吗
Newt, they're hiding something. Okay?
这些人不是像他们说的那样子的
These people are not who they say they are.
不 托马斯 你根本不知道
No, Thomas, you don't know that!
唯一我们知道是他们把我们从实验部那救了出来
The only thing that we do know is that they helped rescue us from WICKED.
他们给我们新衣服 给我们食物 给我们正常的床
They gave us new clothes. They gave us food. They gave us a proper bed.
我们有些人很长时间没有的东西
Some of us haven't had that in a long time.
是 但你
Yeah, but…
我们有些人比其他人更长时间
Some of us a lot longer than others.
嘿 托马斯
Hey, Thomas.
搞什么…
What the…
你拿到了 对吧
You got it, didn't you?
对 我们出发吧
Yeah. Let's go.
好吧 听着 也许你们是对的 也许我只是有妄想症
All right, look, maybe you guys are right. Maybe I'm just being paranoid.
但我要去确认一下 就给我掩护
But I got to find out for sure. Just cover for me.
我会尽快回来
I'll be back as soon as I can.
这是什么啊？
What the hell?
特丽莎
Teresa?
是瑞秋
It's Rachel.
他们在第一晚就带走她了
They took her the first night.
我跟她说过会没事的
I told her it was going to be okay.
你确定这不能再等了吗
You sure this can't wait?
她很明确 长官
She was very specific, sir.
她要你亲自跟她谈谈
She wanted to speak with you personally.
好像我没能力处理好似的
As if I don't have enough to deal with.
就等我一下 我们在受到风暴的干扰
Just bear with me. I'm getting some interference from the storm.
来吧 这够好了 快连接吧
Come on. It's good enough. Make the connection.
晚上好 佩姬博士
Good evening, Doctor Paige.
很高兴再见到你
Lovely to see you again.
虽然我承认我…
Although I admit…
我没有料到这么快收到你的消息
I wasn't expecting to hear from you quite so soon.
计划有变 詹森
Change of plans, Janson.
我会比预期早一点到 就明天
I'll be arriving a little sooner than expected. First thing tomorrow.
你能来我们会很高兴的
We'll be delighted to have you.
我想你会对我们取得的进展感到满意的
I think you'll be pleased with the progress we've made.
正如你所见 前期的成果都是非常有前途的
As you can see, early results have been extremely promising.
无论你在那里对他们做的是什么 这已经有效了
Whatever it is you've been doing to them in there, it's working.
还不够好
Not well enough.
我刚收到董事会的批准
I just received board approval.
我要所有剩下的研究对像进入昏迷状态 准备收割
I want all the remaining subjects sedated and prepped for harvest
我在到达前做好
by the time I arrive.
佩姬博士 我们会尽快完成的
Doctor Paige, we are going as fast as we can.
我们还在测试中
We are still running tests…
做得再快点
Try something faster.
知道我能保证他们安全 这是最好的计划
Until I can guarantee their security, this is the best plan.
长官 安全是我的工作 我们这是24小时封锁的
Ma'am, security is my job. We're on 24 hour lockdown here.
我向你保证
I am assuring you…
实验体都是安全的
the assets are secure.
你找到干将了吗
Have you found the Right Arm?
还没有
Not yet.
我们一直在山上跟踪他们
We tracked them as far as the mountains.
那么他们还在外面
So they're still out there.
而且他们已经攻击了我们2个设施
And they've already hit two of our installations.
他们跟我们一样都想要这些孩子 而我不能…
They want these kids as badly as we do. And I cannot…
我不能再承受其他损失了
I cannot afford another loss.
起码不能在我接近成功研制出解药时
Not now, when I am so close to a cure.
如果你不能完成任务 我会另找其人
If you are not up to the task, I will find someone who is.
没这个必要
That won't be necessary.
我建议我们从最近的新人开始
Might I suggest we start with the most recent arrivals.
就快去完成它
Just get it done.
詹森
Janson.
我不想他们感觉到任何痛苦
I don't want them to feel any pain.
他们什么都感觉不了
They won't feel a thing.
托马斯
Thomas!
我们要走了 我们要走了
We gotta go. We gotta go right now.
- 你在说什么 - 你说「我们要走了」是什么意思
- What the hell are you talking about? - What do you mean, "We gotta go?"
你们必须要来 来吧 我们要走了
They're coming. Come on. We gotta go.
他们要找我们了
They're coming for us.
- 佩姬 她还活着 - 在那里发生什么事
- Paige. She's still alive. - What happened in there?
阿里斯 发生什么事
Aris, what happened?
托马斯 你能冷静下来跟我们说吗
Thomas, can you just calm down and talk to us.
- 她还活着 - 她是谁 特丽莎？
- She's still alive. - Who's she? Teresa?
艾娃
Ava.
Ava?
你能转过身来跟我们说吗
Will you just turn around and talk to us?
这是实验部
It's WICKED!
这里还是实验部
It's still WICKED.
这一直都是实验部
It's always been WICKED.
托马斯
Thomas.
你看见什么了
What did you see?
快来 快来
Come on, come on.
好了 我们走吧
Okay, let's go.
你们快走 有些事我必须要去做
You guys go ahead. There's something I gotta do.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
相信我 这很重要 你们想离开这里 对吧 就快走吧
Trust me, it's important. You guys wanna get outta here, right? Just go.
我跟他一起去
I'll go with him.
好的 温斯顿 走吧 快点
Okay, Winston, go! Go! Come on.
你确信我们能相信这孩子
You sure we can trust this kid?
你不会想知道你在外面是谁
You don't want to know where we'd be without him.
你们在外面这干什么
What are you kids doing out?
我要封锁这里 叫所有人进来
I want this place locked down. Call everyone in.
除非死了 不然任何人都不许离开
No one leaves until everyone's accounted for.
如果你看到他们就告诉我
Tell me you've got eyes on them.
还在寻找 还在寻找
Still looking, still looking.
快点 快点
Come on, come on, come on.
那里
There.
这是谁
Who is that?
克劳福德 他们在找那个女孩
Crawford. Going after the girl.
带所有人去医疗区
Get everyone to the med wing.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
我要他们活着
I want them alive.
别动
Freeze!
原地别动
Stay where you are!
- 为什么他们会向我们开枪 - 我已经在阻止他们
- Why are they shooting at us? - I've spotted them!
- 他们在L-3 - 米诺
- They're in L-3! - Minho!
- 我在跟踪 - 你他妈的在干什么
- I'm in pursuit! - What the hell are you doing?
米诺
Minho!
该死的 米诺
Shit, Minho!
好了 我们走 来吧 我们走吧
Okay. Let's go. Come on. Let's go.
克劳福德博士 你来这里是…
Dr. Crawford, are you here to…
等等 好 好
Wait, wait. Okay, okay.
她在哪
Where is she?
Where is she!
去那里
Get over!
蹲下
Get down!
- 特丽莎 - 蹲下
- Teresa. - Get down!
- 好 伸出你的手 - 照他说的做
- Okay, hands, give me your hands! - Just do what he says.
他们对你做什么了
What did they do to you?
托马斯
Thomas?
把你的手给我
Give me your hands!
你们永远也逃不掉的
You're never gonna get away with this.
发生什么事
What's going on?
我们要马上离开这里 马上 来吧
We gotta leave right now. Come on.
大伙 他们来了 我们该去哪
Guys? They're coming! Where do we go?
费平 让开
Frypan! Move!
回去 回去
Get back! Get back!
他们把门挡住了 叫后援
They've got the door barricaded. Send backup!
大伙 我们得离开这里
Okay, we gotta get outta here!
我们该从哪走
Where do we go?
推
Push!
我们被困住了
Everyone stand back!
纽特 来帮忙
Newt! Help, help!
好了吗？
Ready?
走 走 走
Go, go, go!
让开
Get out of the way!
快点 快点
Come on, come on!
- 快点 - 让人去另外一边
- Come on, come on! - Get someone on the other side!
小心你脚下
Watch your feet!
- 快点 走 - 快点 快点
- Hurry! Let's go! - Come on, move! Move! Move!
托马斯
Thomas!
我们走吧
Let's go!
跟着我
Stay behind me!
该死的 来吧
Shit. Okay, come on!
站住
Stop!
就是这 就是这 快点
There it is! There it is!
全部向3层靠拢
Converge on level 3.
所有人员
All R-16 personnel…
使用非致命性武器
non-lethal force only.
见鬼 快点
Shit. Come on!
不 不 不
No, no, no!
托马斯
Thomas!
打开门 詹森
Open this door, Janson!
你不会真的这么想
You really don't want me to.
打开这该死的门
Open the damn door!
听我说 我是想救你的命
Listen to me! I'm trying to save your life.
暂不说迷宫是一回事 但你们在焦土区不会维持到
The maze is one thing, but you kids wouldn't last one day…
1天的
out in the Scorch.
如果环境杀不死你 毒虫会杀你们的
If the elements don't kill you, the Cranks will.
托马斯 你得相信我
Thomas, you have to believe me.
我只是为了你好
I only want what's best for you.
是啊 让我猜猜 实验部是好的
Yeah, let me guess. WICKED is good?
你们不会通过那道门的 托马斯
You're not getting through that door, Thomas.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
快点
Come on!
托马斯 来吧 我们走
Thomas! Come on! Let's go!
上 上 上 阻止他
Go, go. Stop him!
关上主走廊门
Shut the main vault door!
- 不 - 托马斯
- No! - Thomas?
快来 托马斯 快
Come on, Thomas! Come on!
- 走 走 - 托马斯 怎么回事
- Move! Move! - Thomas, what's going on?
快
Come on.
你个小混蛋
You little shit.
来吧 托马斯 我们走吧 快来
Come on, Thomas. Let's go. Come on!
来吧 继续跑
Come on. Keep moving!
快点 快点
Come on. Come on!
快点 快
Come on, come on!
成扇形散开
Fan out!
来吧 继续跑
All right, come on. Keep going!
见鬼
Shit.
来吧 快走 我们会在风暴里甩掉他们的
Come on, go! Go! We'll lose them in the storm!
所用人员打开视觉通讯器
Notify on visual.
收到
Copy that.
我可以看见他们在围墙这里
I can see them over here at the fence!
走 走 走 低点 低点
Everybody, go, go, go. Stay low. Stay low!
特丽莎 等一下 我们要呆在一起
Teresa, hang on. Stay together!
我觉得我们甩掉他们了
I think we lost them!
继续走 伙计们 快点
Keep going, guys. Let's go…
小心 我们到底在去哪里
Watch out! Where are we even going?
快点 阿里斯 我们走 快点
Come on, Aris. Let's go. Come on!
来这里
Over here!
来吧
Come on!
- 特丽莎 等等 不 不要进去 - 特丽莎
- Teresa, wait! No, don't go in there! - Teresa!
下来这里
Get down here!
- 好吧 来吧 - 进去
- Okay, come on! - Get inside!
来吧 我们走 进去这里
Come on, we should go.
阿里斯 进去
Aris, get in!
我们走吧 大伙
Let's go, guys.
你抓住这吗
Can you hold onto this?
我们在哪里
Where the hell are we?
我们得快点走
We gotta go.
- 我们要继续走 - 不 托马斯 停下来
- We gotta keep moving. - No. Thomas, stop!
告诉我怎么回事
Tell me what's going on.
是实验部
It's WICKED.
是实验部 他们骗了我们 我们从来就没逃离过
It's WICKED. They lied to us. We never escaped.
我和阿里斯 我们找到尸体
Me and Aris, we found bodies.
多的数不清楚
Too many to count.
你是什么意思 尸体
What do you mean? Dead bodies?
不是 但他们也不是活人
No, but they weren't alive either.
他们把他们吊起来了
They had them strung up.
他们身上插满管子
With tubes coming out of them.
他们被…
They were being…
他们被抽干了
They were being drained.
我们的体内有实验部想要的东西
There's something inside of us that WICKED wants.
一些在我门血液里的东西
Something in our blood.
所以我们要尽可能的离他们远点
So we have to get as far away from them as possible.
好吧 那么计划是什么
Okay. So, what's the plan?
你有计划的 对吧
You do have a plan, right?
对 我不知道
Yeah. I don't know.
我们跟着你来到这里 托马斯
Well, we followed you out here, Thomas…
而现在你说你不知道我们在去哪
and now you're saying that you have no idea where we're going…
或者我们要干什么
or what we're doing.
等等 詹森说过些什么关于有人藏在山里
Wait. Janson said something about people hiding in the mountains.
类似反抗的人或军队
Some kind of resistance or army.
干将
The Right Arm.
干将 如果他们真的跟实验部对抗
The Right Arm. If they're really against WICKED,
也许他们能帮我们
maybe they can help us.
人 在山里 山里的人
People. In the mountains. Mountain people.
这就是你的计划
That's your plan?
这是我们唯一的机会
It's the only chance we have.
嘿 大伙
Hey, guys.
看看这个
Check this out.
米诺 灯照过来
Minho, give me a light!
有人来过这里
Someone's been down here.
来吧 打门打开
Come on. Open up.
看起来像有人生活在这里
Looks like people lived here.
而他们现在去哪里了
Where are they now?
我们拿点这些东西
Let's pack some of this stuff up.
任何你觉得可能需要的
Anything you think you might need.
我们分开走 看看还能找到什么 再回这里会合
We'll split up, see what else we can find. Meet back here.
等等 托马斯
Wait, Thomas.
我们走吧
Let's go.
托马斯
Thomas.
什么事
Yeah?
那些留在那里的孩子
All those kids that we left behind back there.
我不想像他们那样结束生命
I don't want to end up like that.
嘿
Hey.
你在听我说吗
Do you hear me?
嗯 我在听
Yeah, I hear you.
很好 我们在这找什么
Good. Now, what are we looking for out here?
生命迹象
Signs of life.
人 生存者 任何能帮我们的人
People. Survivors. Anyone who can help us.
他算不算
Does he count?
见鬼
Shit.
他们有电源
They had power.
你还好吗
You all right?
我没事
I'm fine.
什么
What?
你去哪了
Where did you go?
这看起来还可以用
This looks promising.
嘿 米诺 等等
Hey, Minho. Wait!
托马斯 小心
Thomas, watch out!
后退 后退
Get back, get back!
天啊
Jesus.
她的眼睛
Her eyes!
噢 天啊
Oh, shit.
后退
Stay back!
这他妈的是什么
What the hell is that thing?
快走 走
Gotta move! Go!
快
Go!
- 顶住 - 什么
- Hold it down! - What?
- 顶住 - 米诺 你在干什么
- Hold it down! - Minho, what are you doing?
小心 小心
Watch out! Watch out!
快跑 快跑
Go, go, go!
我们快离开这里
Let's get the hell out of here!
见鬼
Shit.
怎么回事
What's going on?
我不知道
I don't know.
嘿
Hey!
快跑
Run!
Go!
不是吧
Shit!
嘿
Hey!
走
Go!
离开这里
Get outta here!
跑
Run!
快点
Come on!
我们快跑 快跑
Let's go, go, go!
快跑
Let's go!
托马斯 米诺 这些是什么鬼东西
Thomas, Minho, what the hell are those things?
我不知道 就继续跑吧
I don't know. Just keep going!
快跑 快跑
Move! Move!
我们要跑去哪里
Where do we go?
跟上 快来
Come on, keep moving!
我们快跑
Let's go.
哦 见鬼
Oh, Shit!
- 阿里斯 不要 - 不
- Aris, no! - No!
走 绕过去
Go! Go around!
特丽莎
Teresa!
米诺 来吧
Minho, come on!
来吧 快跑
Come on, come on!
我们该去哪里
Where the hell are we gonna go?
我们得找到离开这里的方法
We gotta find a way out of here!
快跑
Go!
跑快点 快点
Faster, faster!
- 纽特 - 纽特
- Newt! - Newt!
伙计们 救救我
Guys, help!
纽特 你你没事吧
Newt, you good?
没事 谢谢 托马斯
Yeah. Thanks, Tommy.
- 快点 纽特 - 不要停
- Come on, Newt! - Keep going!
穿过这里 穿过这里 快点 他们来了
Through here, through here! Let's go! They're coming!
天啊 我们在去哪里
Guys, where are we going?
跟上 快点 跟上
Okay, run! Go! Go!
- 不要停下来 - 快点 他们来了
- Just keep going! - Come on, they're coming!
这是条死路
It's a dead end!
快带我们离开这里 托马斯
Get us out of here, Thomas!
这边
This one!
我拖延他们
I'll hold them back!
大力点
Harder!
快把门打开
Get that door open!
动作快点
Move!
快 费平 我们走
Come on, Frypan! Let's go!
快点 门开了
Come on! It's open!
大家过去 快点 快点
Everyone through! Come on! Come on!
温斯顿
Winston!
救命啊
Help me!
救人 快
Help! Please!
用力拉 天啊
Please! Oh, my God!
快走 快走
Go, go, go!
- 起来 温斯顿 - 快
- Get up, Winston! - Hurry!
米诺 走吧 我随后就来
Minho, go! I'm right behind you!
快跑 快跑
Let's go! Let's go!
托马斯 进来
Thomas. Get in.
嘿 快离开这里
Hey! Get out of here!
他们跑了吗
Are they gone?
是的 我们目前安全
Yeah, I think we're safe for now.
好 我们应该继续走
Okay, we should get moving.
我们快收拾好东西
Let's pack it up.
阿里斯 来吧
Aris, come on.
费平 温斯顿 我们出发了
Fry, Winston. Let's go.
嘿 兄弟
Hey, man.
你还好吗
You Okay?
这地方发生什么事了
What the hell happened to this place?
我不知道
I don't know.
好像很久没有人在这里待过了
It doesn't look like anyone's been here in a long time.
希望全世界都不像这里吧
I hope the whole world's not like this.
等一下 停下来
Hang on, stop.
你们听到了吗
Do you hear that?
蹲下
Get down!
所有人藏起来 藏起来
Everybody, hide! Hide! Hide!
进去这里 进去
Get in here. In here, in here!
哦 见鬼
Oh, shit.
他们永远也不会停止寻找我们 是吗
They're never gonna stop looking for us, are they?
大家都没事吧
Everyone good?
嗯
Yeah.
就差一点 伙计们
A little further, guys.
一定是这些山了
Those mountains, that's gotta be it.
这是我们要去的地方
That's where we're going.
这很远
That's a long way off.
所以我们最好继续走
Then we better get moving.
温斯顿 嘿 温斯顿
Winston! Hey, Winston!
温斯顿
Winston!
他伤得很严重
He's hurt pretty bad.
我们该做什么
What do we do?
该死的
Shit.
温斯顿 你能听到我说话吗
Winston. Can you hear me?
他还好吗
It's okay.
支持住 温斯顿
Hang in there, Winston.
托马斯
Thomas.
抬起他的脚
Grab his legs.
我抬起了 我抬起了
I got him, I got him.
我们得找到避难所
Gotta find shelter!
谢谢
Thanks.
看起来山越来越近了
It's like they're getting further away.
我们只要继续走 我们就可以走到
We just gotta keep moving. We can make it.
那还有多远？
How's it looking?
有点远
It's a little further.
真不会安慰人啊
That's not very convincing.
嘿 你发生什么事了
Hey, what's going on with you?
他们对我做了些事
They did something to me.
一开始我只是感觉 我像从梦中或什么的醒来
At first it just felt like I was waking up from a dream or something.
然后它们就开始回来了
Then they all started coming back.
你的记忆
Your memories?
你记得些什么
What do you remember?
我记得他们第一次带你来的时候
I remember the first time they brought you in.
我还比你高 而且跑的比你更快
I was taller than you then. And faster.
好吧
Okay.
我记得我们为什么在那里
And I remember why we were there.
我们以为我们能解决这一切问题
We thought we could fix all this.
我觉得我们应该回去
I think we should go back.
- 什么 - 就听我说吧
- What? - Just listen to me.
你在说什么 回去？他们曾经那样对我们做
What are you talking about? Go back? After everything they've done to us.
不 不是那么简单的
No, it's not that simple.
不 我觉得就这么简单
Yeah, I think it is that simple.
不 你不明白
No. You don't understand.
什么 我不明白什么
What don't I understand?
本来一切都很好 直到你…
Everything was fine until you…
什么
What?
没什么
Nothing.
特丽莎 你在告诉我什么
Teresa, what aren't you telling me?
嘿
Hey!
伙计们 下来这里
Guys, get down here!
温斯顿 你在干什么
Winston what are you doing, man?
- 把这个给我 - 怎么回事
- Give me that! - What's going on?
- 发生什么事 - 我不知道
- What happened? - I don't know.
他就站起来拿起枪然后他想…
He just woke up and grabbed the gun and then he tried to…
放回去
Give it back, please.
温斯顿 温斯顿 你还好吗
Winston, are you okay?
它在生长…
It's growing…
在我体内
inside me.
我撑不下去的了
I'm not gonna make it.
求你了 求你了
Please. Please.
别让我变成那些东西的中的一个
Don't let me turn into one of those things.
嘿 纽特
Wait, Newt…
谢谢你
Thank you.
现在 快离开这里
Now, get outta here.
永别了 温斯顿
Good-bye, Winston.
走吧
Go.
没关系的
It's okay.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
托马斯
Thomas.
照顾好他们
Take care of them.
我以为我们应该是免疫的
I thought we were supposed to be immune.
我想不是全部人吧
Not all of us, I guess.
如果温斯顿能被感染
If Winston can get infected…
我们应该假设我们都会
we should assume so can the rest of us.
我从没想到我会这样说
I never thought I'd say it…
我想念林间空地了
I miss the Glade.
嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey-
起来
Get up.
纽特 来吧 我们要走了 起来 费平 阿里斯
Newt, get up. Come on, let's go. Frypan, Aris.
我看见些什么
I see something.
什么 是什么
What is it? What…
看见了吗
You see that?
是光
It's lights.
我们做到了
We made it.
我们走吧 马上走 快走
Let's go. We gotta go. Come on.
来吧 我们走
Come on, let's go. Let's go!
快点
Hurry!
走吧
Go!
跑
Run!
一直跑 快
Keep moving! Come on!
快点
Let's go!
快点 特丽莎
Come on, Teresa!
跑 跑 跑
Go, go, go!
我们越来越近了
We're getting closer!
继续跑
Keep going!
跑进去 快跑
Get inside! Go!
哦 天啊
Oh, shi…
米诺
Minho!
快点帮他
Come help him!
来吧 扶他起来
Come on, get him up.
继续跑
Keep going!
快跑
Go!
跑
Move!
来吧 快点
Come on! Hurry up!
- 快点 - 进去
- Come on! - Get in.
放下他
Put him down.
注意他的头
Watch his head.
谁有电筒
Who's got a light?
米诺
Minho!
- 别这样 醒醒 - 米诺
- Come on, come on. - Minho?
米诺
Minho?
醒醒啊 米诺
Come on, Minho.
醒醒吧 兄弟
Come on, man.
醒来了
There he is.
醒过来了
There you go.
醒过来了 你没事吧
Here you are. Are you okay?
发生什么事了
What happened?
你被闪电击中了
I think you got struck by lightning.
来吧 我们扶他起来
Come on, let's get him up.
小心慢慢的
Nice and slow.
好
Okay.
帮他起来
Let's get him up.
- 你能起来吗 - 嗯
- Think you can get up? - Yep
天啊
Oh, my God.
谢谢 伙计们
Thanks, guys.
嘿
Hey.
这什么气味
What's that smell?
你后面
Behind you!
哦 见鬼 天啊
Oh, shit! Oh, my God.
我看到你们跟我的看门狗见过面了
I see you've met our guard dogs.
你是谁
Who's that?
退后 站后点
Stay back! Stay back!
你们看起来很糟糕啊
You guys look like shit.
来吧 跟我来
Come on. Follow me.
除非你们想跟他们一起呆在这
Unless you want to stay here with them.
哦 天啊
Oh, my-
来吧 跟上
Come on, keep up.
豪尔赫想见你们
Jorge wants to meet you.
谁是豪尔赫
Who's Jorge?
你会知道的
You'll see.
好久没有人从焦土区逃出来了
No one's come out of the Scorch in a long time.
你刚让他很好奇
You've just got him curious.
我也是
And me, too.
我对这地方开始有不好的感觉了
Anyone else starting to get a bad feeling about this place?
我们就听他说 看看他说什么
Let's just hear him out. See what he has to say.
豪尔赫 他们到了
Jorge, they're here.
安静
Quiet.
该死的
Damn it.
你们有过全世界都跟你作对的感觉吗
Do you ever get the feeling the whole world's against you?
有3个问题
Three questions.
你们是从哪来的
Where did you come from?
你们在去哪里
Where are you going?
我有什么好处
How can I profit?
别一次性全回答
Don't all answer at once.
我们要去山上
We're headed for the mountains.
我们在找干将
Looking for the Right Arm.
你意思是你在找幽灵
You're looking for ghosts, you mean.
第2个问题
Question number two.
你们是从哪里来的
Where did you come from?
这是我们的事
That's our business.
嘿
Hey!
放开我
Get the hell off me!
Get the hell off me, man!
闭嘴 你这大娃娃
Shut up, you big baby.
这是什么
What is that?
你是对的
You were right.
什么是对的 她在说什么
Right about what? What is she talking about?
我很抱歉 兄弟
I'm sorry, hermano.
看来你被标记了
Looks like you're tagged.
你是来自实验部的
You came from WICKED.
那就是说…
Which means…
你很有价值
you're very valuable.
很好的计划 托马斯 「就听听这男人说什么」
Good plan, Thomas."Just hear what the man has to say."
这对我们真有效
Really working out for us.
闭嘴吧 米诺
Shut up, Minho.
也许我可以 可以抓到绳子
Maybe I can reach the rope.
在欣赏风景吗
Enjoying the view?
你他妈的想要干什么
What the hell do you want?
这是个好问题
That is the question.
我的人想把你们卖回去实验部
My men want to sell you back to WICKED.
生活教会他们别想太多 我从来都不会这样
Life has taught them to think small. I'm not like that.
有些东西告诉我你也不是这样
Something tells me that you're not either.
是血冲昏我的头 还是这个家伙再说胡话？
Is the blood rushing to my head or is this shank not making any sense?
告诉我你们知道干将些什么
Tell me what you know about the Right Arm.
我以为你说他们是幽灵
I thought you said they were ghosts.
我相信有幽灵的存在
I happen to believe in ghosts.
特别是当我听到他们在电波中喋喋不休时
Especially when I hear them chattering on the airwaves.
你告诉我你知道的 也许我们可以做个交易
You tell me what you know, and maybe we can make a deal.
我们知道的不多
We don't know much.
好吧 好吧
Okay! Okay, all right.
他们藏在山里
They're hiding in the mountains.
而且他们攻击实验部 还有他们有很多孩子
And they attacked WICKED. They got out a bunch of kids.
就这些 我就知道这些
That's it. That's all we know.
喂 豪尔赫
Yo, Jorge.
发什么事
What's going on?
我和我的新朋友们只是在互相了解
Me and my new friends were just getting acquainted.
我们了解完了
We're done now.
嘿 等等 什么 你不是要帮我们吗
Hey, wait. You're not gonna help us?
别担心 兄弟
Don't worry, hermano.
我们会带你们回去你们原来的地方
We'll get you back to where you belong.
吊紧了
Hang tight.
这是要去哪里
Going somewhere?
我们都要去
We both are.
拿上你需要的东西 悄悄地收拾
Pack what you need. Do it quietly.
我们到底要去哪里
Where exactly are we going?
说实话 布伦达 这些孩子是我们的入场券
It's real, Bren. These kids are our ticket.
我们是对的 干将不会拒绝我们
The Right Arm can't turn us away.
马上去
Go now.
好了 我抓到了
Okay. I got it.
米诺 准备好了吗
Minho, ready?
来
Yeah.
抓住 好了 一 二 然后推
Gotcha. Okay. One, two, here we go.
- 准备好了？- 三
- Ready? - Three.
- 不够远 - 见鬼
- Not far enough. - Shit!
一切就位 派人进去
In position. Send them in.
来吧 米诺 大力点推她
Come on, Minho. Push her harder!
见鬼
Shit.
就这样
This is it.
一
One…
二 三
two… three!
好 很好
Yes! Yes!
好了
Okay.
特丽莎 快点
Teresa, hurry!
那么就这样 你就放弃这一切
So what, you're just gonna give it all up?
所有你建立的
Everything you've built?
这里没有未来
There's no future here.
当另一帮人找到这地方会发生什么
What happens when another gang finds this place?
我控制不了 我保护不了你
And I lose control, and I can't protect you.
我不需要你保护我
I don't need you to protect me.
如果你感染了闪焰病毒怎么办
What happens if you get the Flare?
之后 我该怎么做
What am I supposed to do then?
锁上你看着你变成那样？
Chain you up, watch you turn?
向你的头开枪 你是希望我这样吗
Put a bullet in your head? Is that what you expect of me?
换了我 我也会这样做的
I would do the same thing for you.
晚上好
Good evening!
这是灾变的世界：杀戮地带部
This is the World Catastrophe Killzone Department.
我们已经完全包围你们的地方
We have your compound completely surrounded.
你们会发现自己拿了实验部的财产
You find yourselves, through no fault of your own…
虽然责任不在你们
in possession of WICKED property.
巴克利
Barkley.
平安无事的还给我们 而我们会把这当作一个误会
Return them to us unharmed and we'll consider this a simple misunderstanding.
等一下 伙计们
Hang on, Guys…
或你们可以抵抗
Or you can resist…
纽特
Newt!
而你们每一个都会死
…and every last one of you will die.
在病毒消灭我们剩余的人前 不会有太多时间了
It won't be long before the Flare wipes out the rest of us.
治愈的希望就在你们的手中
The hope of a cure lies in your hands.
由你们来选择
The choice is yours.
去带孩子过来
Go get the kids.
你要去做什么
What are you gonna do?
我要去给他播我最喜欢的歌
I'm gonna play 'em my favorite song.
哦 见鬼
Oh, shit.
我们走 我们走
Okay. Let's go, let's go.
我们不想惹到任何麻烦 好吗 我们只是想离开这里
We're not trying to cause any trouble, okay? We just got to get out of here.
是这样吗
Is that so?
詹森 我给你抓住他们了 我现在带他们下来
Janson, I got 'em for ya. I'm bringing 'em down.
别开枪
Don't shoot us.
快点 我们走
Come on. Let's go.
我说 我们走
I said let's go.
你这小混蛋
You little bastard!
好了 来吧
Okay. Come on.
来吧 我们走
Come on! Let's go!
巴克利 你在哪？
Barkley, what's your location?
巴克利 你在吗
Barkley, are you there?
长官 你听到这个了吗
Sir, you hearing this?
这是什么
What is that?
布伦达 快点
Brenda! Hurry!
我们没有太多时间了 我们走 我们走
We don't have much time! Let's go, let's go, let's go!
这边
Right this way!
你一定是在跟我开玩笑
You gotta be kidding me.
B计划 兄弟
Plan B, hermano.
你们想去干将那
You kids wanna get to the Right Arm?
我会带你们去 但你们就欠我一个人情了
I'll lead you to them. But you're gonna owe me.
跟我来
Follow me!
好吧 我们走吧
All right! Let's go!
- 来吧 - 快去 所有人快去
- Come on! - Everyone, go.
走吧
Go! Come on.
- 来吧 - 阿里斯 快点
- Come on! - Aris, come on.
所有单位 往里面走
All units, push in!
他们在顶楼 顶楼
They're on the top floor! Top floor!
我们在上去的路上
We're on the move!
快走
Go!
快 阿里斯 快
Go, Aris, go.
特丽莎 下一个轮到你 来吧
Teresa, you're next. Come on.
布伦达 你在去哪里
Brenda! Where you going?
你快点去 我随后就来
Just go. I'm right behind you.
快点
Hurry.
阿尔法22在追 已经行动
Alpha 22 in pursuit. We're on the move!
布伦达 回应啊 你在干什么
Brenda, come on. What are you doing?
我们要走了
We gotta go!
- 我拿到了 - 快走
- I got it. - Come on.
见鬼
Shit.
找掩护
Take cover!
走 走 走 走
Go! Go! Go! Go!
该死的
Shit!
来吧 快点 我们没有时间了
Come on, hurry! We're running out of time!
- 在东面 - 切断他们去路
- On the east! - Cut 'em off!
我看见他们了
I got eyes on!
这里 跟我来
Here, follow me!
- 喔 喔 喔 - 快点
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. - Come on!
站住 站在原地不动
Stop! Stay right where you are!
该死的
Oh, shit.
我们要抓活的 你绕过去 我追他们
No, we need them. You go around. I'll go after them.
去那里 去那里
Over here. Over here.
孩子 别动
Kid, don't move!
布伦达 我们在去哪里
Brenda, where are we going?
快点 歌快播完了
Hurry! The song's almost over!
天啊
Holy shit!
来吧
Come on.
托马斯 快点
Thomas! Come on!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事 很好
Yeah, great.
不 不 不 我们怎么回去其他人那里
No, no. How are we gonna get back to the others?
别紧张 我要带我们离开这里
Relax. I'm gonna get us out of here.
给你
Here.
为什么你们要帮我们
Why are you helping us?
相信我 这不是我的主意
Trust me, it's not my idea.
豪尔赫似乎认为你们是去避难所的入场票
Jorge seems to think you guys are our ticket to the safe haven.
什么
The what?
你知道的 天堂
You know, paradise.
不受太阳威胁 不受感染
Safe from the sun, free of infection.
据说干将带孩子去那里已经好几年了
Supposedly, the Right Arm's been taking kids there for years.
都是免疫者
Immunes, anyway.
而你知道在哪里
And you know where that is?
不
No.
豪尔赫认识个家伙
But Jorge knows a guy.
马库斯
Marcus.
他曾经
He used to…
他曾经偷运孩子上山
He used to smuggle kids up into the mountains.
如果豪尔赫出去了 那就是他会带你的朋友去的地方
If Jorge made it out, that's where he'll be taking your friends.
如果他出去了
If he made it out?
你问好多问题
You ask a lot of questions.
你能就过来这里帮我打开这个吗
Can you just come over here and help me with this?
麻烦了
Please.
这听起来不对劲啊
Well, that doesn't sound good.
是啊
Yeah.
这下面他们会很疯狂
Down here they'll be full term.
我们走吧
Let's go.
我想是这边
I think it's this way.
你想？
You think?
有人生活在这下面吗
Do people live down here?
太阳风暴逼人到地下
The Solar Storms forced people underground.
豪尔赫说 有很多定居点在这些隧道
Jorge says there's settlements all over these tunnels.
那豪尔赫呢 他是你的父亲
So, what about Jorge? Is he your father?
差不多是吧
Close enough.
事实是 我真的不知道他是谁 他只是一直都在我身边
Truth is, I don't really know what he is. He's just always been there.
而我一直都按他说的去做 不管多愚蠢都会做
And I've always done what he's asked me to do, no matter how stupid.
那么你不觉得干将是真的
So you don't think the Right Arm is real?
我觉得
I think…
相信希望是很危险的
hope is a dangerous thing.
希望杀我的朋友 比闪焰和焦土区加起来的还要多
Hope has killed more of my friends than the Flare and the Scorch combined.
我以为豪尔赫会比他们聪明
Just thought Jorge was smarter than that.
该死的
Damn.
嘿 我觉得可能是这边
Hey, I think it might be this way.
布伦达
Brenda?
这边 看看这
I'm over here. Look at this.
什么 这是什么
What? What is it?
这到底是什么
What the hell is this?
我不知道
I don't know.
天啊
Jesus.
快走 小心
Go, go, go!
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
快点
Come on!
继续走
Keep going!
我们快到了 快跑
We're almost there. Come on.
快点 这边
Come on! This way!
托马斯 快点
Thomas! Come on!
好的
Okay.
- 走 快走 - 快点
- Go, go! - Come on!
继续走
Keep going!
小心
Watch out!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
快点
Come on!
跟我来
Follow me!
嗯 就在你后面
Yeah, I'm behind you.
快走 快走
Go, go, go!
- 好了 快走 - 快
- Okay, go, go! - Come on!
布伦达
Brenda!
你没事吧
You Okay?
没事
Yeah.
等一下 我去找下去的方法
Hang on, I'm gonna find a way down.
布伦达 别动 别动
No, Brenda, don't move. Don't move!
- 快点 - 我不行
- Come on. - I can't.
布伦达 抓住我的手
Brenda, grab my hand.
不 不
No, no!
托马斯
Thomas!
我会抓住你的
I'm going to get to you.
- 布伦达 - 我够不着
- Brenda! - I can't reach!
坚持住
Come on!
布伦达
Brenda!
抓住你了
Got you.
我们可以从这下去 来吧
We can get down here. Come on.
你听到了吗
Hey, you hear that?
你没事吧
You all right?
见鬼
Shit.
布伦达
Brenda…
是 是
Yeah, yeah.
我知道
I know.
我们这就去找马库斯吧
Let's just go find Marcus.
好的
Okay.
尽量融入吧
Try to blend in.
（A区）
你确认是这地方
Are you sure this is the place?
你来是参加派对的
You here for the party?
不是
No.
我们在找马库斯 这是他的地方 不是吗
We're looking for Marcus. This is his place, isn't it?
这是我的地方
This is my place.
你是马库斯
Are you Marcus?
马库斯不再住这里了
Marcus doesn't live here anymore.
你知道我们去哪里可以找到他吗
Do you know where we can find him?
当然 可以 他在B区那边
Sure, sure. He's over in Zone B.
好吧 什么是B区
Okay. What's Zone B?
们烧尸体的地方
It's where they burn the bodies.
嘿 这样 有没有其他人
Okay, look, has anyone else been by here…
来这找过他
looking for him?
一群跟我们一样年纪的孩子 里面有个女孩
Group of kids around our age? They had a girl with them.
黑色头发的
Dark hair.
你知道的 我觉得他们可能在里面
You know… I think they might be inside.
给
Here.
喝这个
Drink this.
这是什么
What is it?
入场券
The price of admission.
喝吧
Drink it!
到你了
Your turn.
好吧
All right.
你们俩 去享受派对吧
You two, enjoy the party.
也许我们应该分开找
Maybe we should split up.
看看找不找到其他人
See if we can find the others.
嘿
Hey.
别喝其他东西
Don't drink anything else.
真好玩
That was fun!
什么
What?
布伦达
Brenda?
他们不在这里
They're not here.
好吧
Okay,
我们得继续找
well… we should keep looking.
为什么
Why?
反正我们也找不到干将了
We couldn't find the Right Arm anyway.
没有马库斯不行
Not without Marcus.
你的朋友都走了
Your friends are gone.
都完了
It's over.
现在只有我们了
It's just us now.
就尽量放轻松
Just try and relax.
放手吧
Let go.
怎么样
How?
像这样
Like this.
怎么啦
What?
你不是她
You're not her.
布伦达
Brenda.
托马斯
Thomas.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 有没有人看见你来这里
Hey. Did anyone see you come here?
没有 你在说什么
No, what are you talking about?
我们没有太多时间了
We don't have a lot of time.
托马斯 怎么啦
Thomas, what's wrong?
我只是 我要见你
I just had to see you…
我有些事情必须向你解释
and just try to explain things before…
噢 不
Oh, no.
托马斯
Thomas!
就听我说 好吗
Just listen to me, okay?
无论你告诉他们关于我什么 无论你说什么
Whatever they tell you about me, whatever they say,
我只需要你知道 我必须要做的
I just need you to know I had to do it.
好吗
Okay?
你做了什么
What did you do?
因为我不能眼瞧着他们死
I just couldn't keep watching them die.
在这里
Over here!
来吧
Come on.
不
No!
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
托马斯
Thomas!
嘿 你会没事的
Hey, you're okay.
嘿
Hi.
我们要停止像这样见面
We have to stop meeting like this.
欢迎回来 丑八怪
Welcome back, you ugly shank.
我建议你快开口 你这狗娘养的
I suggest that you talk! You son of a bitch!
该死的
Damn it!
我很抱歉
I'm sorry…
你们要离开我的房子
you're going to have to leave my house.
看起来你一直玩得很开心啊
Looks like you've been having fun.
听着 我不享受伤害你
Listen. I don't enjoy hurting you.
知道吗
Okay?
干将在哪 马库斯
Where is the Right Arm, Marcus?
等等 这是马库斯
Wait, this is Marcus?
这孩子很快明白啊
The kid catches on quick.
这次行动都听你指挥吗
Are you the brains of the operation?
我知道 你知道他们藏在哪里
I know you know where they're hiding.
所以你告诉我 然后我就跟你做个交易
So you tell me, and I'll make you a deal.
你可以跟我们一起去
You can come with us.
我早就把那座桥烧了
I burned that bridge a long time ago.
还有 交易
Besides, I made my own deal.
是你教会我不错失任何一个机会的
You're the one who taught me, never miss an opportunity.
他在说什么
What's he talking about?
我在说供给和需求
I'm talking about supply and demand.
实验部想要所有他们能找到的免疫者
WICKED wants all the lmmunes they can get.
我提供给他们
I help provide that for them.
所以我引诱孩子进来…
So I lure the kids in…
他们喝醉了他们玩得很开心
they get drunk, they have a good time.
然后晚点… 实验部来了
And then, later, WICKED comes in…
他们从中再挑选出来
they separate the wheat from the chaff.
我改变我的心意了 兄弟
I changed my mind, hermano.
我很享受伤害你
I do enjoy hurting you.
说 说
Talk! Talk!
好了 天啊
Okay! Jesus!
我不能保证任何事
But I'm not making any promises.
这些家伙很喜欢到处转移
These guys like to move around.
他们在山里有个前哨站
They have an outpost in the mountains.
但它在很远
But it's a long way away.
你走到一半实验部就来追你屁股了 你永远也去不到那里
You got half of WICKED on your ass. You're never gonna make it.
靠走路是不行
Not on foot.
贝尔特在哪
Where's Bertha?
贝尔特不行
Not Bertha.
好了 我想我们只能靠走了
Well, I guess we're on foot.
蹲下
Get down!
找掩护
Take cover!
嘿 大家没事吧
Hey, is everyone okay out there?
我们没事
We're fine.
有人知道枪手在哪吗
Anyone know where those bloody shots came from?
狗娘养的 马库斯 他带我们去一个埋伏
That son of a bitch, Marcus. He led us into an ambush.
我们该怎么做
What do we do?
给
Here.
拿着这个
Hold this.
我们要转移他们的注意力
We gotta create a diversion.
你准备好扔出去
You get ready to chuck it.
所有人
Everybody!
准备冲刺回卡车上
Get set to sprint back to the truck!
并堵住你们的耳朵
And hold your ears!
准备好了吗 一
Ready? One…
二
Two…
仍了
Drop it.
马上
Now!
我说 仍了
I said drop it!
站起来 我们走
On your feet. Let's go.
走啊 快
Let's go! Move!
- 往后退 - 放松点
- Back up! - Easy.
你们俩 快过来
You two, over here now!
- 快点 别磨蹭 - 别做傻事 走
- Come on, let's go! - Don't be stupid! Move.
慢点
Slowly.
阿里斯
Aris?
我的天 哈丽特
Oh, my God. Harriet?
我的天 你在这里干什么
My God. What the hell are you doing here?
索尼亚
Sonya.
阿里斯 你很幸运我们没把你屁股打开花
Aris, you're lucky we didn't shoot your dumb ass.
你在那还好吗
You all right, man?
怎么会
How?
发生什么事了
What's happening?
我们以前一起在迷宫里的
We were in the maze together.
我们没危险 伙计们 出来吧
We're clear, guys! Come on out!
收到 我们没危险
Copy that! We're clear!
下来吧
Stand down!
我的天 你还活着
My God, you're alive.
倒车吧 乔
Back it up, Joe!
倒车吧
Back it up!
我们带他们去基地
We're taking them to base.
等等 那么你们是怎么到这里的
Wait, so, how did you guys get here?
- 干将救了我们出来 - 等等
- The Right Arm got us out. - Wait.
干将 你知道他们是谁吗
The Right Arm? Do you know where they are?
上车
Hop in.
他们一直计划这个超过一年了
They've been planning this for over a year now.
这都是给我们的
This is all for us.
你们很幸运找到我们
You guys are lucky you found us when you did.
我们明天天亮就搬走了
We're moving out at first light.
文斯在哪
Where's Vince?
我想在那边某个地方吧
Somewhere over there, I think.
谁是文斯
Who's Vince?
是一个决定你能不能留下的人
He's the one who decides if you get to stay.
我以为干将应该是一支军队啊
I thought the Right Arm was supposed to be an army.
对 我们以前是
Yeah, we were.
这就是我们剩下的的人
This is all that's left of us.
牺牲了好多好人 才换来今天
Lot of good people died getting us this far.
他们是谁
Who are they?
他们是免疫者
They're lmmunes.
在山里碰巧遇上的
Caught 'em coming up the mountain.
你检查过他们了吗
Did you check 'em?
我认识这家伙 阿里斯 我相信他
I know this guy, Aris. I trust him.
我信不过 检查他们
Well, I don't. Check 'em.
嘿 老大
Hey, boss…
布伦达 布伦达
Brenda! Brenda!
怎么回事
What's going on?
布伦达 布伦达
Brenda! Brenda!
布伦达
Brenda.
- 布伦达 说话啊 - 抱歉 我很抱歉
- Brenda, talk to me. - I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
她是怎么回事
What's going on with her?
我不知道 布伦达 你还好吗
I don't know. Brenda, are you all right?
- 布伦达 说话啊 - 怎么回事？
- Brenda? Talk to me. - What the hell?
见鬼
Shit!
- 毒虫 我们有个毒虫 - 不
- Crank! We got a Crank! - No!
- 不 - 等等 等等…
- No! - Wait, wait!
- 退后 - 听我说
- Step back! - Listen, okay?
这是刚发生的 好吧 她还没有危险
This just happened, okay? She's not dangerous yet.
你们不应该带她来这里
You shouldn't have brought her here!
我知道
I know.
如果我们让毒虫进来这里 避难所就持续不了一周
We let Cranks in here now, the safe haven doesn't last a week!
- 退后 - 好的 我明白
- Step back! - I understand, okay?
我明白
I understand.
就听我说 拜托
Just listen. Please.
求你了 好吗 我告诉过她你能帮她
Please, okay? I told her that you could help.
行不行 不行
Okay? No.
肯定有些什么你可以做的
There's got to be something you can do.
对 肯定有
Yeah, there is.
- 我可以帮她从她的痛苦解脱 - 不
- I can put her out of her misery. - No!
不要
No!
文斯 够了 放开他
Vince, that's enough! Let him go.
放开他
Let him go!
她被感染了 医生 没什么我们能对她做的了
She's infected, Doc. There's nothing we can do for her.
不 但他可以
No, but he can.
你好 托马斯
Hello, Thomas.
什么
What?
你认识我
You know me?
有意思
Interesting.
他们还是把你放进迷宫里了
It makes sense they'd put you in the maze.
虽然我必须承认
Though I must admit…
我很担心 他们在你做了那种事后会杀了你
I was worried they'd kill you after what you did.
哪种事？
What I did?
我们第一次交谈时 你说你再也承受不了
The first time we spoke, you said you couldn't take it anymore…
看着你的朋友一个个的死
watching your friends die, one by one.
我们最后一次交谈
The last time we spoke…
你给我所有实验部 试验和实验室的具体坐标
you gave me the coordinates of every WICKED compound, trial and lab.
原来你是我们的内线
He was our source.
没有他我们就不能拯救那么多人出来
We couldn't have pulled all this off without him.
带她到帐篷里
Take her to the tent.
给这些人拿些厚点的衣服
Get these guys some warm clothes.
小心点
Careful.
好吧
Come on.
嘿 这是我们起码能做的
Hey, it's the least we can do.
托马斯 来吧
Thomas, come on.
我们需要从你这取点血液样本
I need to get some blood from you.
一开始 我们就迷失了方向
In the beginning, we were lost.
我们唯一知道的是
All we knew for sure…
你越年轻 机会就越大
was that the younger you were, the stronger your chances.
你跟实验部工作的
You worked for WICKED?
很久以前了
Long time ago.
你知道在一开始 我们是有最好的目的
You know, at first, we had the best intentions.
找出解药 拯救世界
Find a cure, save the world.
很显然你们就是关键… 因为你们是免疫者
It was clear you kids were the key, because you were immune.
但为什么
But why?
最终他们找到了答案
Eventually, we found an answer.
由大脑产生的一种酶可以免疫
An enzyme produced by the brains of the immune.
一旦从血液中分离出来
Once separated from the bloodstream…
就可以成为一种有效的药 减缓病毒的蔓延速度
it can serve as a powerful agent to slow the spread of the virus.
那么你找到了解药
So, you found a cure?
不完全是
Not exactly.
酶不能人造 只能从免疫者身上提取
The enzyme can't be manufactured, only harvested from the immune.
只有孩子有
The young.
当然这不会让实验部止步
Of course, that didn't stop WICKED.
如果他们有他们的方法
If they had their way…
他们会牺牲一整代人
they'd sacrifice an entire generation.
全都为了这个
All for this.
进化得出的生物礼物
A gift of biology.
进化
Of evolution.
但一个不意味着我们所有人都能认同
But one not meant for all of us.
她能活多久
How long will that give her?
每个人都不同 也许几个月吧
It's different for everyone. A few months maybe.
不过很难说 是不是？
But that's the catch, isn't it?
总是越多越好
She'll always need more.
好了
Okay.
我们出去外面吧 让她休息下
Let's go outside. Let them rest.
走吧
Let's go.
她会没事的
She'll be fine.
托马斯
Thomas.
你知道她不能跟我们一起 对吧
You know she can't come with us, right?
他是我的兄弟
He was my brother.
嘿 抱歉
Hey. Sorry.
你没事吧 你感觉怎么样
Are you okay? How are you feeling?
你让我想起了他
You remind me of him.
他永远都能看到人最好的一面
He always saw the best in people.
他现今在哪了
Where is he now?
我不知道
I don't know.
当我们还是孩子的时候…
When we were kids…
我们被其中一个实验部营带走了
we were taken in by one of WICKED's camps.
他们给我们做了一大堆测试
They gave us a bunch of tests.
他们不要我
They didn't want me.
可是他们想要他
They wanted him, though.
他们甚至不让我道别
They didn't even let me say good-bye.
他叫什么名字
What was his name?
乔治
George.
这是查克
That was Chuck.
他是怎么死的
How did he die?
为了救我
Saving my life.
好好休息
Get some rest.
老弟
Hermano.
如有有任何事发生在她身上 我…
If anything were to happen to her, I…
我知道 我知道
I know, I know.
你进去 跟她聊聊吧
You should get in there. Go talk to her.
我想现在是我欠你了
I guess I owe you, now.
我们冲出来了 这是实话
So we broke out. I'm telling the truth.
我希望阿尔比可以看见这一切
I wish Alby could've seen all this.
还有温斯顿
And Winston.
还有查克
And Chuck.
他们会为你感到骄傲的 你知道的 汤米
He'd be proud of you, you know, Tommy.
是啊
Yeah.
嘿 阿里斯
Hey, Aris!
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys!
我有点喜欢这孩子
I kinda like that kid.
是啊 虽然我还是不相信他
Yeah. I still don't trust him, though.
嘿 特丽莎在哪
Hey, where's Teresa?
她上那里去了
She went up there.
嘿 你没事吧
Hey, you okay?
你在上面这里干什么
What are you doing up here?
只是在想事情
Just thinking.
好吧 我让你一个人呆着吧
All right, I'll let you be alone.
你还记得你的母亲吗
Do you remember your mother?
记得
I think so.
我记得我的
I remember mine.
她是一个很漂亮的女人
She was a beautiful woman.
所有人都喜欢她
Everybody loved her.
在实验部来之前她是我的一切
And before WICKED, she was all I had.
当她生病了 我不知道该怎么做
When she got sick, I didn't know what to do.
我只是把她关起来 藏好
I just kept her locked up. Hidden.
我想她会好起来
I thought she'd get better.
每天晚上 她都会发出很可怕的声音 就像尖叫
Every night, she'd make these awful sounds, like screaming.
然后有一晚她没有叫了
And then, one night, she just stopped.
终于安静下来了
She was finally quiet.
我去她的房间
I went down to her room.
发现满房都是血
And there was blood everywhere.
但她只是坐在那里 很平静
But she was just sat there, calm.
她说她感觉好点了
She said she was feeling better.
我的愿景实现了 她治好了她的病
The visions were gone. She'd taken care of them.
她把她的眼睛挖了出来 托马斯
She took her eyes out, Thomas.
外面有上百万人在受苦
There are millions of people suffering out there.
有上百万个跟我一样的故事
Millions of stories, just like mine.
我们不能背弃他们
We can't turn our backs on them.
我不会的
I won't.
什么… 你在说什么
What… What are you saying?
我在说我要你理解
I'm saying, I want you to understand.
理解什么
Understand what?
为什么我这样做
Why I did it.
特丽莎
Teresa…
求你别反抗他们 托马斯
Please don't fight them, Thomas.
你做了什么
What have you done?
不要
No!
好了 下去吧 伙计们 包围他们
All right, drop in, boys. Round 'em up.
跑 快离开
Go, go!
把他们拿下
Take 'em out!
泰森
Tyson!
- 站住 - 别动
- Stop! - Don't move!
托马斯在哪
Where's Thomas?
哈丽特 拿弹药来
Harriet! Ammo!
文斯 哈丽特
Vince! Harriet!
- 快 - 来这里
- Come on! - Over here!
有什么要我帮忙的？
How can we help?
你来掩护我们
You need to cover us!
弹药
Ammo!
嘿 你知道怎么用吗
Hey! Do you know how to use this thing?
掩护我
Cover me!
这可能是我们唯一的机会
This fifty's our only chance!
布伦达
Brenda!
你这蠢货
You dumb-ass.
快点
Come on!
干嘛 你这是想找死吗
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
我们快找掩护
We gotta take cover!
我们现在必须走了 趁我们还有机会
We have to go. Now, while we still have the chance.
我要去找其他人
I gotta go find the others.
不 你看看那里 看
No! Look! Look.
你帮不了他们
You can't help them.
文斯 快点 他们太多人了
Vince, hurry up! There's too many of them.
我没弹药了
I'm out!
小心
Look out!
该死的
Shit!
好了 放我下去
All right, take me down.
哦 见鬼
Oh. Shit.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你没什么能帮得上他们
There's just nothing you can do for them.
如果我们不马上走 我们也好不到哪里去
If we don't move now, we won't be much better off.
你们要马上离开
You guys gotta go right now.
什么
What?
他们要的不是你们
They're not looking for you.
你们会安全的 但你们应该马上离开
You'll be safe, but you have to go now.
托马斯
Thomas…
我不能离弃他们
I can't leave without them.
走
Go.
祝你好运 孩子
Good luck, kid.
布伦达 我们要走了 快点
Bren, we have to go. Come on. Come on.
我们走吧 快 快
Let's go, come on. Come on!
我们走 快点
Let's go, let's go!
- 你没事吧 - 没事
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
让他们排成一排 都跪下 抬眼往上
Line them up right here! On their knees! Put some eyes up on that ridge.
B-4
B-4.
我们抓到多少人
How many did we get?
差不多全部人吧
All of them. Give or take.
什么差不多
Give or take what?
哦 跑了几个
Well, they lost a few.
A-4
A-4.
A-6
A-6.
B-3
B-3.
托马斯在哪
Where's Thomas?
我在这
Right here.
别的
Freeze!
走
Go!
托马斯
Thomas.
把他排到队里
Get him in line.
好了
Okay.
带她进来
Bring her in.
为什么你不跑
Why didn't you run?
我不想再逃跑了
I'm tired of running.
这是所有的人了吗
Is this all of them?
大部分
Most of them.
这就够了
It'll be enough.
开始装货
Start loading them in.
是 长官
Yes, ma'am.
好了 你们都听到了 走吧
Okay, you heard. Let's go!
带他们上去
Get 'em on!
你好 托马斯
Hello, Thomas.
我很高兴你没事
I'm glad you're safe.
怎么回事
What the hell?
特丽莎
Teresa?
等等 怎么回事
Wait, what's going on?
她是跟他们一伙的
She's with them.
什么时候开始的
Since when?
特丽莎总是明白牺牲小我 成就多数的人
Teresa's always had an evolved appreciation of the greater good.
重置她的记忆 只是时间的问题
Once we restored her memories, it was only a matter of time.
进去 进去
Let's go, let's go.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我没有选择 这是唯一的出路
I had no choice. This is the only way.
我们必须找到解药
We have to find a cure.
她是对的 这一切只是为了达到目的的一种手段
She's right. This is all just a means to an end.
你以前是很理解的 托马斯
You used to understand that, Thomas.
无论你怎么看我
No matter what you think of me…
我不是怪物 我是一个医生
I am not a monster. I'm a doctor.
我发过毒誓要找到解药
I swore an oath to find a cure!
无论付出什么代价
No matter the cost.
我只需要多一点时间
I just need more time.
更多的血
More blood.
你好 玛丽
Hello, Mary.
我一直希望我们能再次见面
I hoped we'd meet again.
我很抱歉在这种环境再相遇
I'm sorry it had to be under these circumstances.
我也有很多事情感到很抱歉 但这不是其中之一
I'm sorry about a lot of things, too. But not this.
至少我有良心
At least my conscience is clear.
我也是
So is mine.
玛丽 玛丽
Mary? Mary?
玛丽
Mary!
玛丽 玛丽
Mary! Mary!
放开我
Get off me!
玛丽 玛丽
Mary? Mary?
玛丽
Mary?
不要…
No!
玛丽 不
Mary! No!
快点 詹森
Come on, Jansen.
带他们上飞机 我们走吧
Load them up. Let's go.
这些人 杀掉他们
All these people. Get rid of them.
我们走 我们走
Let's go. Let's go!
放开我
Let go of me!
索尼亚 阿里斯
Sonya! Aris!
退后
Get back!
所有人 别过来
Everyone, stand back!
- 后退 - 别开枪
- Stand back! - Hold your fire!
- 所有人 别过来 - 别开枪
- Everyone, stand back! - Hold your fire!
- 退后 放他们走 - 托马斯 把炸弹放下
- Stand back. Let 'em go. - Thomas, put it down.
- 放他们全部人走 - 你知道我不能这样做
- Let 'em all go! - You know I can't do that!
托马斯 求你别这样
Thomas, please stop.
我跟他们做了个交易 他们保证我们会没事的 我们全部人
I made a deal with them. They promised we'd be safe. All of us.
现在 我应该相信你了？
And I'm supposed to trust you now?
没错 这是她唯一的条件
It's true. It was her only condition.
闭嘴
Shut up!
一切都可以回到原来的样子
Everything can go back to the way it was.
托马斯
Thomas…
你真的想他们都死吗
do you really want all of them to die?
听她说的吧 托马斯 想想你在干什么
Listen to her, Thomas. Think about what you're doing.
我们支持你 托马斯
We're with you, Thomas.
不
No.
不要
Don't.
- 引爆吧 托马斯 - 我们准备好了
- Do it, Thomas. - We're ready.
不要回去那里
We're not going back there.
托马斯
Thomas?
这是唯一的出路
It's the only way.
托马斯
Thomas!
- 快走 快走 - 带她离开这里
- Come on. Come on! - Get her out of here!
你没事吧
You good?
别动 把它放下 孩子
Freeze! Drop it, kid!
快跑 趴下
Run! Get down!
别动
Freeze!
真浪费
What a waste.
文斯 快走
Vince, go!
快
Now!
保持住 我瞄准你了
Keep going. I got you.
快离开这里 快跑
Get outta here! Go! Go!
快点 托马斯 快离开这里
Come on, Thomas! Get outta here!
米诺 我们走吧
Minho, let's go!
快离开这里 跑啊
Get out of here! Go!
蹲下
Get down!
米诺
Minho!
- 托马斯 回来 - 不 托马斯 不
- Thomas, get back! - No! Thomas, no!
米诺
Minho!
托马斯
Thomas!
不要
No!
米诺
Minho!
快跑 来吧
Go! Come on!
米诺
Minho!
我们现在该怎么做
What do we do now?
现在我们重整我们剩下的人
Well, we pick up what's left of us.
我们按计划进行
We stick to the plan.
带你们去安全港
We get you kids to the safe haven.
然后我们重新开始 我想是这样吧
Then we start over, I guess.
我不会跟你们去的
I'm not going with you.
什么
What?
我答应过米诺
I made a promise to Minho.
我不会离弃他 而且我要去找他
I wouldn't leave him behind. I have to go after him.
嘿 孩子 看看你周围 好吗
Hey, kid, look around you.
实验部刚重击了我们
All right? WICKED just kicked our ass.
你想想你该去哪里
You think about where you're headed.
我没有要求你们跟我一起去
I'm not asking anyone to come with me.
托马斯 听我说
Thomas, listen to me.
我认识了米诺…
I've known Minho for…
从我有记忆起
Well, as long as I can remember.
所以如果有任何方法…我们可以救他
So, if there was any way that we could help him…
相信我 我会在那里跟你一起
trust me, I would be up there standing next to you.
可是 你在说的这个…
This, what you're talking about…
是不可能的
is impossible.
更像是自杀
More like suicide.
也许吧
Maybe.
但我现在知道我应该做什么了
But I know what I'm supposed to do now.
这不只是为了米诺 是为了我们所有人
It's not just about Minho. It's about all of us.
所有实验部抓过 还有要抓的人
It's about everyone WICKED's ever taken, everyone they will take.
他们永远也不会收手
They'll never stop.
他们永远也不会收手 那我来帮他们收手
They'll never stop, so I'm gonna stop them.
我要去杀了艾娃·佩姬
I'm gonna kill Ava Paige.
我必须承认
I have to admit…
我很喜欢以牙还牙
I'd like some revenge.
话说的很动听 小子
Well, that's a good speech, kid.
那么 你的计划是什么呢
So, what's your plan?